megaupload.net 2016-06-16

# Sanda Soap Company

NAVIGATION

CONTACT

SOCIAL

MADE IN THE U.S.A. ROCKFORD IL. 61103

LOCATION

Privacy Policy updated -  Sandra Soap Company  Revised 3-27-2016 This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Sandra Soap Company collects, uses, maintains and discloses information  collected from users of the www.sandrasoapcompany.com website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and  services offered by Sandra Soap Company. Personal identification information We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit  our site, register on the site place an order fill out a form respond to a survey subscribe to the newsletter and in connection with  other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name,  email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can  always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site  related activities. Non-personal identification information We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal  identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of  connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.  Web browser cookies Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping  purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to  alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. How we use collected information Sandra Soap Company collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests  and support needs. To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use  the services and resources provided on our Site. To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we  receive from you. To process transactionsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to  provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to  provide the service. To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive  about topics we think will be of interest to them. To send periodic emailsThe email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them  information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other  requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company  news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from  receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact  us via our Site.  How we protect your information We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized  access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and  data stored on our Site. Third party websites Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers,  sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not  responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their  content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer  service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to  that website(s) own terms and policies. Changes to this privacy policy Sandra Soap Company has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the  bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are  helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this  privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Your acceptance of these terms By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not  use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of  those changes. Contacting us  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us  at:Sandra Soap Company1015 Ridge Ave  Rockford IL. 61103 E-Mail:[Info@SandraSoapCompany.com](mailto:Info@SandraSoapCompany.com)

Privacy Policy updated -  Sandra Soap Company  Revised 3-27-2016 This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which  Sandra Soap Company collects, uses, maintains  and discloses information collected from users  of the www.sandrasoapcompany.com website.  This privacy policy applies to the Site and all  products and services offered by Sandra Soap  Company. Personal identification information We may collect personal identification  information from Users in a variety of ways,  including, but not limited to, when Users visit  our site, register on the site place an order fill  out a form respond to a survey subscribe to the  newsletter and in connection with other  activities, services, features or resources we  make available on our Site. Users may be asked  for, as appropriate, name, email address,  mailing address, phone number, credit card  information. We will collect personal identification  information from Users only if they voluntarily  submit such information to us. Users can always  refuse to supply personally identification  information, except that it may prevent them  from engaging in certain Site related activities. Non-personal identification information We may collect non-personal identification  information about Users whenever they interact  with our Site. Non-personal identification  information may include the browser name, the  type of computer and technical information  about Users means of connection to our Site,  such as the operating system and the Internet  service providers utilized and other similar  information.  Web browser cookies Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User  experience. User's web browser places cookies  on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes  and sometimes to track information about  them. User may choose to set their web browser  to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies  are being sent. If they do so, note that some  parts of the Site may not function properly. How we use collected information Sandra Soap Company collects and uses Users  personal information for the following purposes: To improve customer serviceYour  information helps us to more effectively  respond to your customer service  requests and support needs. To personalize user experienceWe  may use information in the aggregate  to understand how our Users as a  group use the services and resources  provided on our Site. To improve our SiteWe continually  strive to improve our website offerings  based on the information and feedback  we receive from you. To process transactionsWe may use  the information Users provide about  themselves when placing an order only  to provide service to that order. We do  not share this information with outside  parties except to the extent necessary  to provide the service. To administer a content, promotion,  survey or other Site featureTo send  Users information they agreed to  receive about topics we think will be of  interest to them. To send periodic emailsThe email  address Users provide for order  processing, will only be used to send  them information and updates  pertaining to their order. It may also be  used to respond to their inquiries,  and/or other requests or questions. If  User decides to opt-in to our mailing  list, they will receive emails that may  include company news, updates,  related product or service information,  etc. If at any time the User would like  to unsubscribe from receiving future  emails, we include detailed unsubscribe  instructions at the bottom of each  email or User may contact us via our  Site.  How we protect your information We adopt appropriate data collection, storage  and processing practices and security measures  to protect against unauthorized access,  alteration, disclosure or destruction of your  personal information, username, password,  transaction information and data stored on our  Site. Third party websites Users may find advertising or other content on  our Site that link to the sites and services of our  partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors,  licensors and other third parties. We do not  control the content or links that appear on these  sites and are not responsible for the practices  employed by websites linked to or from our Site.  In addition, these sites or services, including  their content and links, may be constantly  changing. These sites and services may have  their own privacy policies and customer service  policies. Browsing and interaction on any other  website, including websites which have a link to  our Site, is subject to that website(s) own terms  and policies. Changes to this privacy policy Sandra Soap Company has the discretion to  update this privacy policy at any time. When we  do, revise the updated date at the bottom of  this page,. We encourage Users to frequently  check this page for any changes to stay  informed about how we are helping to protect  the personal information we collect. You  acknowledge and agree that it is your  responsibility to review this privacy policy  periodically and become aware of  modifications. Your acceptance of these terms By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of  this policy and terms of service. If you do not  agree to this policy, please do not use our Site.  Your continued use of the Site following the  posting of changes to this policy will be deemed  your acceptance of those changes. Contacting us  If you have any questions about this Privacy  Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings  with this site, please contact us at:Sandra Soap  Company1015 Ridge Ave  Rockford IL. 61103 E-Mail:[Info@SandraSoapCompany.com](mailto:Info@SandraSoapCompany.com)

SOCIAL
